Guide to the Global Fund for Women Records SC0671
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2015-060
  - Records
    - The Right to Self - Determination (Coeur d'Alene, ID), October 30, 1993, 1993 Oct 30 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Women Organzining, November 1993, 1993 Nov (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Women, Money, and Empowerment, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Nepal "Kaval gulhati" February 1994, 1994 Feb (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Hemispheres Interview, March 1994, 1994 Mar (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Female Rights: An International Health Perspective: May 9, 1994, 1994 May 9 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Proposed Book: Women from Dawn to Dusk, June 1994, 1994 Jun (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Sierra, September/October 1994 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Global Network - September/October 1994 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Women's Rights - Soroptomist Pacific Region (Palo Alto) October 22, 1994, 1994 Oct 22 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - AWID Newsletter, November 1994, 1994 Nov (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Correspondence from Anne Firth Murray, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Population and Women's Issues, Stanford May 1995, 1995 May (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - A Women's Fundraising Handbook, August 1995, 1995 Aug (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Mothers and Children, August 1995, 1995 Aug (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - The UN's Fourth World Conference on Women and NGO Forum, October 1995, 1995 Oct (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Murray Speehes, October 1995, 1995 Oct (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - WAFUNIF, October 20, 1995, 1995 Oct 20 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Proposals Under Review, November 16, 1995, 1995 Nov 16 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Articles and Correspondence 1996 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Speeches by Anne Firth Murray 1996 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Bay Area Business Women's Calendar, March 1996 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - FAQ on Global Fund for Women, March 1996 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Poverty, Women's Rights and the Global Economy, April 1996, 1996 Apr (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Proposals Under Review - May 1, 1996, 1996 May 1 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Foundation - News and Commentary (Magazine), May/June 1996 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Directions: Partners of the Americas, September/October 1996 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - NetWorthy, Fall 1996 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Viewpoint, February 10, 1998, 1998 Feb 10 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Independent Sector, Fall 1999 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - McGann Women and Health Series, Stanford University - October 8, 2001, 2001 Oct 8 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Invitation to Women's Health at Stanford, January 2002, 2002 Jan (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Human Biology Newsletter, Spring 2006, 2006 Spring (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Bay Area Business Woman, November 2006, 2006 Nov (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - New Zealand's Anti-Nuclear Stance (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Global Fund Offers Minigrants for Women's Equality and Leadership (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Woman of Power (Issue 24) (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Leon A. Farley Associates (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Past History (LA, NY, DC) (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Files for Anne Murray (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Anne Murray - Email Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Grantmaking Criteria (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Booklets (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - GFW: Information and Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Grants (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Articles on GFW (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Transition notes and cards (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - CEO and Leadership, 1985-1994 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Advisory Council 1998-1990 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - A Report to the Global Fund for Women on its Long Range Strategy, February 1990, 1990 Feb (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Grants - Strategy, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - New Zealand Evening Post, May 27, 1992, 1992 May 27 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Long Range Plan, 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Richard L. Meier, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Workplan, June 1993, 1993 Jun (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Board, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Women, Money, and Empowerment, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Financial Management Group, January 1994, 1994 Jan (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Financial Management Group, February 1994, 1994 Feb (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Financial Management Group, March 1994, 1994 Mar (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Financial Management Group, April 1994, 1994 Apr (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Financial Management Group, May 1994, 1994 May (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Financial Management Group, June 1994, 1994 Jun (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Financial Management Group, July 1994, 1994 Jul (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Finanial Management Group, August 1994, 1994 Aug (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Finanial Management Group, September 1994, 1994 Sept (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Leon A. Farley Associates - Mary Ann Stein, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Leon A. Farley Associates - Patty Wilson, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Board, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Strategic Planning, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - CEO and Leadership, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Board of Directors' Handbook, December 1995, 1995 Dec (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - CEO and Leadership, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Transition Files, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Future/Goodbyes, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Board, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - The Circle, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Fund for Future, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Study Retreat on Sex Trafficking and Forced Prostitution, Februrary 13-14 1996, 1996 Feb 13-14 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Kavita N. Ramdas, June 1996, 1996 Jun (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Actions for the Future: Plans and Programs, June 1996, 1996 Jun (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Board of Directors, June 2, 1996, 1996 Jun 2 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Transition Meeting II August 28, 1996, 1996 Aug 28 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Report on Global Fund Workshops at the AWID Conference, September 1996, 1996 Sept (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Proposals Under Review, April 9, 1997, 1997 Apr 9 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Letter to Board Members, November 1997, 1997 Nov (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Leader to Leader, Summer 1998 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Gender and Grantmaking, April 1999 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (San Francisco) May 2001 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Mission Pamplets - undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Strategic Planning - Misc. undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - GFW - The Third Year, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Strategic Planning, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Strategic Planning - Misc. 1991-1994; 1998-2002 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Women Organizing, November 1993, 1993 Nov (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - GFW - Workplan, 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Strategic Planning - Misc. 1994 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Results of the Consultation for the Strategic Planning Process, July- September 1994 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Background of the Strategic Planning Process, October 1994, 1994 Oct (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - GFW - The Eighth Year, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Young Women Leaders Program - Beijing, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Literature Review, January 16, 1995, 1995 Jan 16 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Strategic Planning - Misc. January-February 1995 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Notes on Criteria for Grantmaking, February 6, 1995, 1995 Feb 6 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Strategic Plan Update #1, February 10, 1995, 1995 Feb 10 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Social Movement Interviews, April 26, 1995, 1995 Apr 26 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Strategic Planning - Misc. May-June 1995 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Strategic Planning Process, October 1995, 1995 Oct (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Input on Drafting of Document, October 30, 1995, 1995 Oct 30 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Strategic Planning - Misc. October-December 1995 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Draft of Plan and Programs Document, December 5, 1995, 1995 Dec 5 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Looking to the Future - Plans and Programs, 1995-1999 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Actions for the Future, 1995-2000 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Looking to the Future, 1995-2000 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - GFW - Workplan, 1996-2000 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Actions for the Future - Workplan, 1996-2000 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Actions for the Future - Plans and Programs, 1996-2000 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Strategic Planning - Misc. January 1996, 1996 Jan (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Strategic Planning - Misc. February 1996, 1996 Feb (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - State of Global Fund and other Thoughts, June 1996, 1996 Jun (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Honoring Women, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Weaving and Repairing - Annual Report, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Proposals Under Review, March 16, 1998, 1998 Mar 16 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Proposals Under Review, September 29, 1998, 1998 Sept 29 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Raising our Voices, July 1999, 1999 Jul (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Annual Report, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Daring to Lead: A Strategic Plan, May 2003, 2003 May (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Women Daring to Lead - Annual Report, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Our Values and Who We Are, August 2004, 2004 Aug (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Global Fund for Women Annual Report, 2004-2005 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Global Fund for Women, Annual Report, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Computer Files (Box 8)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-008
  - Consent Docket, 2000 Jul (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Consent Docket, 2000 Mar (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Consent Docket, 2000 Sep (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Consent Docket, 2000 Nov (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Consent Docket, 2001 Feb (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Consent Docket, 2002 Jun (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Consent Docket, 2002 Sep (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Consent Docket, 2002 Dec (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Consent Docket, 2003 Mar (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Consent Docket, 2003 Jun (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Consent Docket, 2003 Jun (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Consent Docket, 2003 Sep (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Consent Docket, 2004 Apr (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Consent Docket, 2004 Jun (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Consent Docket, 2004 Oct (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Consent Docket, 2004 Dec (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Consent Docket, 2005 Apr (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Consent Docket, 2005 Jun (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Consent Docket, 2005 Sep (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Consent Docket, 2006 Jan (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Consent Docket, 2006 Sep (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Board of Directors, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Grantmaking program, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Proposals under review, 1999 Feb (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - GFW: Africa Initiative, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Actions for the future, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - From program officers to Anne, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Les femes, l'argent et le pouvoir, Dakar, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - GFW: Women, money, and empowerment, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - GFW: Study trip to Europe, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - GFW: Meeting of the circle on sex trafficking forced prostitution, 1996 Feb 13-14 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Grant lists, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Advisory Council, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - China, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Academia Mexicana de Derechos Humanos, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - UN convention on elimination of all forms of discrimination against women, 2000 Mar (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Letters to Anne Firth Murray from 6FW BOD, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - GFW end of fiscal year report, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Proposals under review by Region, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - GFW: A Journalist's View, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 1995 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Fundraising letters and initiatives, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Women organizing: a report from GFW, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - GFW - investing in women, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Honoring women campaign, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Clippings: hemispheres, 1994 Mar (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Clipping: the country almanac, 1992 Jul 8 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - 15 years, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Women Transforming the World - 10th Anniversary, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - 10th anniversary, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Reports, 1987-1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Grants Lists, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Mission brochures, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Promotional packet, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - FAQ, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - A Women's Fundraising Handbook, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - GFW Network News, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Raising our voices newsletter, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)